[
	{
		"question": "While it has <b>Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon</b> as material, <b>Number C62: Neo Galaxy-Eyes Prime Photon Dragon</b> is unaffected by the opponent's:",
		"choices":
		[
			"monster effects",
			"spell effects",
			"activated effects",
			"targeting effects"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "The effect of <b>Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon</b> to banish itself and the monster it battles is:",
		"choices":
		[
			"once per turn",
			"once per chain",
			"once per duel",
			"once per battle"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "The Galaxy user in the Yu-Gi-Oh! ZEXAL anime is named:",
		"choices":
		[
			"Yuma Tsukumo",
			"Reginald Kastle",
			"Kite Tenjo",
			"Don Thousand"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of the following is not treated as a Galaxy card?",
		"choices":
		[
			"Galactikuriboh",
			"Starliege Lord Galaxion",
			"Numbers Last Hope",
			"Numeron Creation"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of the following can be overlaid directly on top of <b>Galaxy-Eyes Cipher X Dragon?</b>",
		"choices":
		[
			"Galaxy-Eyes Full Armor Photon Dragon",
			"Galaxy-Eyes Cipher Dragon",
			"Galaxy-Eyes Cipher Blade Dragon",
			"Galaxy-Eyes Solflare Dragon"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "How many Photon and/or Galaxy cards are currently on the TCG banlist?",
		"choices":
		[
			"0",
			"1",
			"2",
			"3"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of the following is true?",
		"choices":
		[
			"All Photon monsters are LIGHT attribute, but not all Galaxy monsters.",
			"All Galaxy monsters are LIGHT attribute, but not all Photon monsters.",
			"All Galaxy and Photon monsters are LIGHT attribute.",
			"No Galaxy and Photon monsters are LIGHT attribute."
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "There exists no Photon or Galaxy card of this card type:",
		"choices":
		[
			"Ritual",
			"Tuner",
			"Fusion",
			"Pendulum"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "<b>Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon</b> can be special summoned by tributing two monsters with:",
		"choices":
		[
			"Galaxy or Photon in their name",
			"total levels equal to 8",
			"LIGHT attribute",
			"2000 or higher attack"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "How many cards are simultaneously Galaxy and Photon, besides xyz monsters?",
		"choices":
		[
			"0",
			"1",
			"2",
			"3"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "<b>Number 38: Hope Harbinger Titanic Galaxy</b> can do all of the following except:",
		"choices":
		[
			"negate spell effects",
			"remove monsters' xyz material",
			"redirect attacks",
			"increase the attack of monsters"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Can the search effect of <b>Photon Orbital</b> be negated by <b>Called By The Grave?</b>",
		"choices":
		[
			"Yes",
			"No",
			"Only if the exact Photon Orbital activating the effect is targeted",
			"Only if a different Photon Orbital was targeted prior to its activation"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "<b>Photon Lizard</b> is:",
		"choices":
		[
			"a dragon",
			"a reptile",
			"a cyberse",
			"a wyrm"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "In the Yu-Gi-Oh! ARC-V anime, an alternate version of the Galaxy user in ZEXAL is present, now with a deck of:",
		"choices":
		[
			"Raidraptors",
			"Constellars",
			"Satellarknights",
			"Ciphers"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "There exists no Photon or Galaxy card of this monster type:",
		"choices":
		[
			"Insect",
			"Fairy",
			"Dinosaur",
			"Beast"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "The only monster you control is <b>Number C62: Neo Galaxy-Eyes Prime Photon Dragon</b>. It has as material <b>Galaxy-Eyes Photon Dragon</b>, <b>Galaxy-Eyes Afterglow Dragon</b>, and <b>Photon Emperor</b>. There are no cards in your hand or GY. How much attack can that monster achieve in the Battle Phase?",
		"choices":
		[
			"5600",
			"6400",
			"11200",
			"12800"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "The additional normal summon offered by <b>Photon Emperor</b> is:",
		"choices":
		[
			"a continuous effect",
			"an activated effect",
			"an unclassified effect",
			"a condition"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "The targeting protection offered by <b>Galaxy-Eyes Cipher X Dragon</b> applies to monsters summoned later in the turn only:",
		"choices":
		[
			"in the OCG",
			"in the TCG",
			"in Master Duel",
			"in Duel Links"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "The highest attack achievable by <b>Galaxy Brave</b> with its own effect is:",
		"choices":
		[
			"3200",
			"4000",
			"4500",
			"5000"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "<b>Tachyon Transmigration</b> can only be activated from hand if you control:",
		"choices":
		[
			"a \"Tachyon\" monster",
			"a \"Galaxy-Eyes\" monster",
			"a \"Galaxy-Eyes Tachyon Dragon\" monster",
			"Number 107: Galaxy-Eyes Tachyon Dragon"
		],
		"answer": 2
	}
]